<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>davewrites</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on davewrites</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:34:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://davewrites.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sudoku</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_003/</guid><description>Rain trickled down the window and the patter of water on glass filled the study. Smoke rose from the single cigarette burning uselessly in the ash tray. The lights were off but John had not noticed, this had been the fourth night this week he&amp;rsquo;d been up late trying to solve this puzzle. How many minutes had he spent trying to write just a fourth digit down. It would not add up, numbers one through nine add up to forty-five, six boxes equal 270, he starting counting, 21, 46, 72, John lost count and threw the sudoku at the wall.</description></item><item><title>Student life</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_002/</guid><description>Steam rose from the mug by the screen&amp;rsquo;s side, packets of cereal bars covered the table, some even covering the numpad of the keyboard. A student sat at the desk, their head leaning into their hand, their elbow firmly pressed against the table. One headphone was in the right ear and the video of a lecture occupied their screen. From behind you would not be able to tell if they were awake or asleep.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:40:47 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/about/</guid><description>I am a doctor and a writer. I am currently on my journey of writing my first novel and have started the habit of writing every day. Here you will find my 100 word story series, updates on my novel writing and book/audiobook reviews.</description></item><item><title>Running</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 17:53:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</guid><description>The trainers in the drawer had been used once. They were an immaculate white colour with a central blue stripe across either side. Today they would get stained, today I felt empowered. I hauled myself out of my sofa, the imprint on the cushion breathed a sigh of relief as it inflated slightly. Fortunately I was already wearing gym kit as I wore gym kit most days anyway. I coughed, tied the laces and lumbered to the door.</description></item></channel></rss>