<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on davewrites</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on davewrites</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 17:53:56 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Running</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 17:53:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</guid><description>The trainers in the drawer had been used once. They were an immaculate white colour with a central blue stripe across either side. Today they would get stained, today I felt empowered. I hauled myself out of my sofa, the imprint on the cushion breathed a sigh of relief as it inflated slightly. Fortunately I was already wearing gym kit as I wore gym kit most days anyway. I coughed, tied the laces and lumbered to the door.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>The trainers in the drawer had been used once. They were an immaculate white colour with a central blue stripe across either side. Today they would get stained, today I felt empowered. I hauled myself out of my sofa, the imprint on the cushion breathed a sigh of relief as it inflated slightly. Fortunately I was already wearing gym kit as I wore gym kit most days anyway. I coughed, tied the laces and lumbered to the door. I crossed the threshold and put one foot in front of the other, I was now a runner.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>FirstPost my first blog post is about coding which is complicated.</description><content type="html">&lt;h1 id="firstpost">FirstPost&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>my first blog post is about coding which is complicated.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>