<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on davewrites</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on davewrites</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Student life</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_002/</guid><description>Steam rose from the mug by the screen&amp;rsquo;s side, packets of cereal bars covered the table, some even covering the numpad of the keyboard. A student sat at the desk, their head leaning into their hand, their elbow firmly pressed against the table. One headphone was in the right ear and the video of a lecture occupied their screen. From behind you would not be able to tell if they were awake or asleep.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>Steam rose from the mug by the screen&amp;rsquo;s side, packets of cereal bars covered the table, some even covering the numpad of the keyboard. A student sat at the desk, their head leaning into their hand, their elbow firmly pressed against the table. One headphone was in the right ear and the video of a lecture occupied their screen. From behind you would not be able to tell if they were awake or asleep. Behind the computer screen you could see the dark campus lit only by street lights. The video then stopped playing, the student did not move.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>Running</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 17:53:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/post_001/</guid><description>The trainers in the drawer had been used once. They were an immaculate white colour with a central blue stripe across either side. Today they would get stained, today I felt empowered. I hauled myself out of my sofa, the imprint on the cushion breathed a sigh of relief as it inflated slightly. Fortunately I was already wearing gym kit as I wore gym kit most days anyway. I coughed, tied the laces and lumbered to the door.</description><content type="html">&lt;p>The trainers in the drawer had been used once. They were an immaculate white colour with a central blue stripe across either side. Today they would get stained, today I felt empowered. I hauled myself out of my sofa, the imprint on the cushion breathed a sigh of relief as it inflated slightly. Fortunately I was already wearing gym kit as I wore gym kit most days anyway. I coughed, tied the laces and lumbered to the door. I crossed the threshold and put one foot in front of the other, I was now a runner.&lt;/p></content></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://davewrites.co.uk/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>FirstPost my first blog post is about coding which is complicated.</description><content type="html">&lt;h1 id="firstpost">FirstPost&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>my first blog post is about coding which is complicated.&lt;/p></content></item></channel></rss>